Clock Hand Angle 1.1 by Aohan Dang

Description
Find the angle between the hour hand and minute hand of a clock by inputting the hour, minute,
and second. You can choose to have an approximate decimal answer or a fractional exact answer.

How to install and run
Send angclock.89f to your TI-89 or TI-89 Titanium. The correct syntax for this function is
angclock(hour,minute,second,f) in which f is 1 if you want a fractional answer and f is 0 if you
want a decimal answer. For example, to find the angle at 9:45:06 in fractional form, the syntax
is angclock(9,45,6,1).