Gamma Function by Aohan Dang

Description
Extend the domain of the factorial function to all complex numbers except negative real numbers.

How to install and run
Send _GAMMA_.89f to your TI-89 or TI-89 Titanium. The correct syntax for this function is
Γ(number). You can enter the Γ by searching through the character list or Var-Link. If you are
finding the gamma of not a whole number, set the function to return an approximate decimal
by changing a mode setting or pushing diamond, then ENTER. The relationship between Γ and ! is
Γ(n)=(n-1)!. If you attempt to find the gamma of a negative number, you will not get an accurate
answer.